Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1874-1944; 39.0 boxes
  - Subseries 1D: Short Stories, 1893-1895; 3.0 boxes
    - Prose Stories and Beginnings, 1895; 36.0 folders
      - "If the reader is one who occasionally visits the neighborhood...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "If you should fall in with a yeoman...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "There is a charms about our own outlying country lanes...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "The Seven Days", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "A Snow Storm", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "Ballade of an Evile", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7a)
      - "A Blight in Egypt", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "The Buttonwood Inn stand at a country corner...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "The Club", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "A Critical Moment" by Captain Robert S. Brownson [pseudonym for Harrison S. Miller?], dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "A Country turnpike on a warm midsummer's day...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "The Crowd was gathering every minute...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "An Exchange of Cards", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "The House of the Hopewells stood white and conspicuous...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "In the midst of a city of many thousand souls lived Henry Pimpernal", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - "An Indian Officer's Idyll", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - "Jaggers has swooned on Broadway", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - "Men and Women of the July", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - "Mr. Brown's Advertisement", 1895; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      - "A Ripping Tale", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
      - "Roger Coil's Life Theme", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
      - "Slumberside Lies in a deep valley...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
      - "The Spite of a Telegraph Pole", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
      - "There was a certain attractiveness about Miss Mulder...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
      - "There was a man whose strange personality...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
      - "There were two light hearts upon the steamer Williamsport...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 27)
      - "A Traitoress", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 28)
      - "A Turkish Bath", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 29)
      - "...the way the more often he was to be found upon it..." (incomplete), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 30)
      - "We were all invited, Will, Archie, Grace, and Ida...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 31)
      - "Whoever saw Dick Dove", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 32)
      - "Winter's Day Tale" Morning, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 33)
      - "Ye Mystick Four", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 34)
      - Unidentified, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 35)
  - Subseries 1E: Non-Fiction -- Books, 1912-1929; 4.0 boxes
    Consists of manuscript works of non-fiction by Harrison Morris, including "A Brief History of a Great House Confessions in Art," 1929.
    - Characters of the Literary Nineties and After, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1-6)
    - A Brief History of a Great House Confessions in Art, 1929; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - A Brief History of a Great House Confessions in Art (cont.), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1-4)
    - A Brief History of a Great House Confessions in Art (cont.), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1-7)
    - Walt Whitman: A Brief Biography with Some Reminiscences, 1929; 1.0 item (Folder 1-4)
    - William T. Richards: Masterpieces of the Sea, 1912; 1.0 item (Folder 5-6)
  - Subseries 1F: Essays, 1877 January 8-1941 October; 3.0 boxes
    Consists of manuscript essays of Harrison Morris, including "Is There an American Art?" and "Retro-spective," 1892-1922.
    - Papers to Put in Your Pipe, dates not examined; 18.0 folders
      - Title page, table of contents, and miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "At Cobb's Corners", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Books I Have Rambled With", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "Buds and Books", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "The Centaur" (translated from the French of Maurice de Guerin), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "A Good Word for the Accidental", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "The Limbo of Ideals", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "A Little Journey Afoot", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "A Little-known Poet", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "Mountain Echoes", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "Mr. Hollidge", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "On a Cane I Lost", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "On Some Lapses in Observation", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "Snow Drift", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "The State Fair--A Day Off", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "Taste": TMs, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - "Two Epitaphs", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - "Wings of Morning", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
    - "An Actor's Convention", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - "Agnes Repplier", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - "Among the numerous walking routes that ran hither and thither about Bryn Mawr...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - "Anecdote o Psyche Knot" (Jules Lefebore, "Note on mother and Child"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - "Anecdotes of John G. Johnson", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
    - "Anne Hollingsworth Wharton", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - "The announcement of Governor Hayes' election...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - "An Appeal to Reason", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - "Anybody who attempts to enclose Joseph Wharton in two hundred and fifty words...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
    - "Art and Artifice in Italy", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
    - "Art Education", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
    - "The Architectural Work of Frank Miles Day & Brother", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
    - "The Art and Life of Thomas Eakins" (for Philadelphia Art Week, 1931 October 21; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
    - "Art as a Teacher", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
    - "Art Criticism From an Artist' standpoint", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
    - "Author's at home--S. Weir Mitchell in Walnut Street", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
    - "The Babylonian Expedition" of University of Pennsylvania, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
    - "Benjamin West", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
    - "Between the Mansion House at West Chester and Kenneth Square...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
    - "A Blot in the Scutcheon", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
    - "Briefly, what is the average idea about poetry?", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
    - "The Candid writer of a...of Will Carlton in Harpers...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
    - "The Career of Robert Vonnoh", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
    - "Charles B. Brown", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
    - "The City" Centennial of 1876, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
    - "Coverage", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
    - "The Delaware at Dawn", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 27)
    - "A Daniel Come to Judgment", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 28)
    - "Denmark", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 29)
    - "Every Jeames, Being a microscopic analysis of an American Abroad", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 30)
    - "Essay on Shelley", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 31)
    - "The Fire and the Future", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 32)
    - "The Footpath Way", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 33)
    - "The Futility of Criticism", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 34)
    - "The Future of American Literature", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 35)
    - "The grouping together of the four or five women who are now beginning to paint in Philadelphia...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 36)
    - "Harrison S. Morris Speaks his Faith in Franklin D. Roosevelt" for Committee of Independent Voters, 1941 October; 1.0 item (Folder 37)
    - "Has there ever been a female poet?", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 38)
    - "I had long ago built a Concord in the reaches of my fancy...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 39)
    - "Historic Houses" Contemporary with Germantown's Battle, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 40)
    - "I sometimes think if a man could describe any particular visitation...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 41)
    - "Ibsen's: A Doll's House" (Drama Review), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 42)
    - "In a critical estimate of the poets of America...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 43)
    - "In ivory carving the Japanese excel...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 44)
    - "In My Day", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 45)
    - "In my day as Director of the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts..." (re: "Elder" Widener), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 46)
    - "In the September number of Lippincott's Magazine...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 47)
    - "The Inarticulate Soldier", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 48)
    - "Intangible Property", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 49)
    - "Is anybody guileless enough to suppose that a huge conspiracy to enrich the few...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 50)
    - "Is the Ballot a Remedy?", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 51)
    - "Is There an American Art?", 1922 January 10; 1.0 item (Folder 52)
    - "Isn't it time that we of Philadelphia come together...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 53)
    - "It is taken for granted that [we] must have read 'The Ring and The Book'...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 54)
    - "Jena Leon Gerome Ferris" (from the Dictionary of American Biography), 1930; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - "John Blighton", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - "John Bunyon", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - "John McClure Hamilton: A Study", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - "Joseph Wharton", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
    - "The Knowledge that Keats was an apprentice to a surgeon...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - "The Last Fishwoman", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - "Literary Average", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - "Lord Chesterfield", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
    - "The Man of My Town", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
    - "The Management of the Germantown Library", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
    - "The Masque of 1916", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
    - "The Memorial Exhibition of Sixty Paintings by Thomas Eakins" (Metropolitan Museum of Art), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
    - "Mine Ease in Mine Inn", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
    - "Miss Oakley's Mural Decorations", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
    - "[Moonlight] and snow are a spectral fellowship...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
    - "The Music of the earth--breathing from wood and grass..." (Newport Concert), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
    - "A New American [Sculpture/Sculptor]", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
    - "New Year's Day ushered in an old-fashioned snowstorm...", 1877 January 8; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
    - "Old Salem and Hawthorne", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
    - "On Being Polite", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
    - "Our Tuesday evening last, at Parker's Hall...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
    - "The Paintings of Thomas Eakins" (Metropolitan Museum of Art), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
    - "Plain Living with Beauty", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
    - "Promptings of a High Romance", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
    - "A Symphony", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
    - "Tanner's Show--December 1908", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 27)
    - "There are several sorts of portraits...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 28)
    - "There has been a great deal said lately on the glory of Philadelphia...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 29)
    - "There is a tendency to regard the current trend...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 30)
    - "Thomas Eakins" (for the Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York City), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 31)
    - "Through a lifetime of dabbing in books..." (re: Keats), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 32)
    - "Through the window [pane]", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 33)
    - "To any traveler fond of idling across the country...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 34)
    - "To the watchful observer of literary development...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 35)
    - "The traditional jack-tar has almost disappeared...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 36)
    - "Racketeering", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 37)
    - "Retro-spective", 1892; 1.0 item (Folder 38)
    - "Robert Vonnoh, ...", 1934 January 24; 1.0 item (Folder 39)
    - "The Romance of Collecting", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 40)
    - "The Romantic Movement of the Early XIX Century", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 41)
    - "Samuel Pepy's Diary", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 42)
    - "Slang as a Literary Element", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 43)
    - "Some Official Sketches", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 44)
    - "The State Fair--A Day off", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 45)
    - "Travels Near Home", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 46)
    - "Violet Oakley's belongs to Philadelphia...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 47)
    - "Violet Oakley's Decorations", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 48)
    - "Walter Savage Landor", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 49)
    - "The Were-Wolf", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 50)
    - "Wings of Morning", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 51)
    - "A Word about Keats", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 52)
    - "Why Keats is Best", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 54)
    - Unidentified, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 55)
  - Subseries 1G: Articles, 1897-1939; 2.0 boxes
    Consists of magazine and newspaper articles written by Harrison Morris, 1897-1939.
    Organized by form and arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Scribner's Magazine, 1897-1920; more than 6 folders
      - "The John G. Johnson Collection of Art", 1920; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "On the Painting of Childhood", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "The Paintings of John McClure Hamilton", 1897; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - [skipped], dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "Portraits of Children", 1901; 1.0 item (Folder 5-7)
        Includes autograph manuscripts, correspondence, and pictures.
      - "The Portraits of John W. Alexander", 1899; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - Ladies' Home Journal, 1916-1917; more than 3 folders
      - "The Most Wonderful Pictures in [America] From the Leading Private Collections", 1916 August; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
        (Elkin Collection--Philadelphia)
      - Gardner Collection of Boston, 1916-1917; 1.0 item (Folder 10-11)
      - Miscellaneous Material from Gardner and Johnson Collections, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
    - Newspapers, 1934 June 13-1939; 4.0 folders
      - "Books that Have a Christmas Flavor" ( Philadelphia Bulletin), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Men and Things" (series in Philadelphia Bulletin), 1936-1939; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Pennsylvania in Art Since Gettysburgh" ( Public Ledger), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Philadelphia Bulletin, 1934 June 13; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - Magazines, 1900 February 11-1938 November; more than 11 folders
      - "John McClure Hamilton" ( Evening Ledger for Art Week), 1938 November; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "Mr. Tanner's work shows..." ( Century Magazine), 1900 February 11; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - [skipped], dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "Philadelphia's Contribution to American Art" ( Century Magazine), 1905; 1.0 item (Folder 8-9)
      - "How to Make an [Art] Exhibition" ( Art World), 1917 November; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "Elizabeth Shippe Green" ( The Book Buyer), 1902; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "S. Weir Mitchell" A Study in Vignette ( Book News Monthly), 1907 October; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "The Tendency of Modern Fiction..." ( Town Topics), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "S. Weir Mitchell" ( The Alumni Register--The University of Pennsylvania), 1914 February; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "Scholar and Man of Letters" ( University of Pennsylvania Graduate Magazine), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "Violet Oakley" ( Book Buyer), 1902; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
  - Subseries 1H: Book Reviews, 1896-1927; 17.0 folders
    Consists of reviews of books written by authors such as Sacheverell Sitwell, Charles Morris, Maurice Francis Egan, and H. Nelson Gray.
    - A Banquet of New Books (J. B. Lippincott's Xmas 1896 Listing), 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - "Books for the Holidays", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - The Gothick North by Sacheverell Sitwell, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - A History of the United States and its Institutions by Charles Morris, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - John Keats by Amy Lowell ( "Amy Lowell's John Keats: An Analysis"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
    - Junipero Serra Agnes by Repplier, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - Man and Beast by Samuel Scoville, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - New Gentlemen of the Road by Herbert Walsh, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - Poems of the Longer Flight by Herbert Walsh, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
    - Recollections of a Happy Life by Maurice Francis Egan, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
    - Recollections of a Happy Life by Maurice Francis Egan, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      Published in The Forum.
    - "Remembered Yesterdays" (Robert Underwood Johnson), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
    - Rhymes and Roses by Samuel Mintum Peck, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
    - Socialism and the American Spirit by Nicholas Paine Gilman, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
    - Strenuas Italy, Solvinga Perilous Problem by H. Nelson Gray, 1927; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
    - To Think of Tea by Agnes Repplier, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      For Philadelphia Record.
    - The Yersin Phono-Rhythmic Method of French Pronunciation, Accent, and Diction by M & J Yersin, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
  - Subseries 1I: Papers, Speeches, Conversations, 1889-1944 June; 22.0 folders
    Consists of speeches given by Harrison Morris at locations such as the Franklin Inn, the American Academy of Arts and Letters, and the Contemporary Club, 1899-1938.
    - "Art as a Teacher" (read at Norwood Century Club), 1913 February; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - "The Baby's Toilet by Mary Cassatt", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - "Coleridge Somewhere puts forth the notion..." (re: Robert Tait McKenzie), 1908 August; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - "Fashionable Society: A Lecture by Lincoln L. Eyre", 1889; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - "An Imaginary Conversation Between Mr. Henry James and Mr. Carpenter" (Franklin Inn), 1905 May; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
    - "Into the Mouths of Babes" (Franklin Inn), 1904 April; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - "Personal Recollections of Julia Ward Howe and Her Daughter Maud Howe Elliot", 1944 June; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      Read at the Germantown Historical Society.
    - "When we look back at the path we have trod as a nation..." (Contemporary Club), 1912 April; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - "Art", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
    - "Mark Twain's Hundredth Birthday" (American Academy of Arts and Letters), 1935 November; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
    - "Matthew Arnold said: 'The future of poetry is immense'" (Contemporary Club), 1899 December; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
    - "The Modern Spirit in Painting and Sculpture" (Society of Arts and Letters), 1922; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
    - "The Place an Art Museum Should Occupy in a Municipality" (Contemporary Club), 1920; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
    - "The Poetry of War" (American Academy of Arts and Letters), 1918; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
    - "Quotations from Anthony and Celopatra Notes--by Horace Howard Furness" (Contemporary Club), 1916 March; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
    - "This is the Day of Biography": Anecdotes of Penwomen (Penwomen's Meeting), 1931 February; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
    - "Thomas Hovenden" (Montgomery County Historical Society), 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
    - "2 Ways of running a magazine..." (Penwomen's Meeting), 1929 March; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
    - "We are met to-night to hear from a great, serious heart..." (introduction to John Masefield, Contemporary Club), 1916 January; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
    - "What is the Matter with Philadelphia?" (Contemporary Club), 1938 February; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
    - "Unidentified", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
    - "Conversation--E. S. Martin and Harrison S. Morris" (Life" dinner of the National Institute of Arts and Letters), 1920 January 17; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
  - Subseries 1J: Letters to the Editor, Memorials, Translations, 1912-1944; 36.0 folders
    Consists of letters to the editors of "Philadelphia Record" and "Public Ledger," 1916-1931, as well as memorials for figures such as Theodore Roosevelt and John La Farge.
    - Blurbs, dates not examined; 2.0 folders
      - Art Exhibitions--Maurice Molarsky & Henry B. Snell, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Art Bulletin--"The Entrance of Cleopatra into Tarsus", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1916-1939; 7.0 folders
      - Philadelphia Record (David Stern) re: Philadelphia's finances, 1931; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Philadelphia Record re: William S. Vare, 1929 December 10; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Public Ledger re: Philadelphia Graft, 1917; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Public Ledger re: Art Museum, 1924; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Public Ledger re: John G. Johnson Art Collection, 1923; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Philadelphia Bulletin re: Louis Repplier, 1939; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Public Ledger re: John F. Lewis, 1916; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
    - Memorials, 1912-1925 August 9; 13.0 folders
      - Addison Burke, 1912; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - John Stephens Durham, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - Horace Howard Furness, 1912; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - A. W. Harrison, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - John La Farge, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - Charles Henry Luders, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - Anna Lea Merritt--"The End of a Beautiful Life", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - Mary Moss, 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - Edmund Clarence Stedman, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)